[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
TAKE CHARGE OF MY HEART
We kissed.
My very first kiss…
wasn't anything like the ones in books or dramas.
No bells. No sparks.
But…
the time…
flew by so ****ing fast.
It's morning already.
Ms. Na Bo-bae.
Come out.
I can see you.
Oh.
You're here.
Why'd you hide?
No, I wasn't hiding.
The table looked a bit wobbly,
so I was just checking.
It's fine now.
Ms. Na.
Yes?
I…
Is he about to ask me out now that we've kissed?
Or
does he want another kiss?
It's a kiss.
…need
a charge.
What?
A charge.
Oh.
Right, a charge.
A charge.
What were you imagining?
What? Imagine what?
Let's go. I'll charge you.
What? Where are you going? You said you needed a charge.
Let's do it here.
In your room.
This is
my room?
Don't say no this time.
You should stay in the house. Stop living in the garage.
What are you doing?
I'm just grateful for everything.
Consider it a bonus charge.
You were supposed to charge me anyway.
Seriously? You always do whatever you want.
All right, we're done.
That's enough!
We should apologize to Ms. Na, right?
Should I talk to her first?
Yeah.
Ms. Na.
-Yes? -Well…
It's almost lunchtime.
If you don't have lunch plans with Mr. Baek,
would you like to join us?
Sure.
Wait.
You always have lunch with Mr. Baek.
Are you sure that's okay?
Yes, it's totally fine.
Great! Let's go have something nice.
Sounds good.
Who said you could do that?
Wow.
It's been a long time since we had lunch together, sir.
We just had a team dinner in Jeju.
Yes. You're right.
We did. Silly me.
Lunch with Ms. Na
was part of my routine.
But she agreed to have lunch with you so readily.
That surprised me.
Sir.
We felt like we owed her an apology,
so we asked her to lunch.
Well, you see…
When the rumors about you and Mr. Ji started spreading,
I believed them and treated you coldly. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I mean, they even figured out you were a drama writer, so--
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
It's hard to know what to believe with rumors like that. I understand.
How could you judge someone like that?
Reflect on your actions.
It's really okay. Please enjoy your meal.
Ms. Na.
Do you really have no feelings for Mr. Ji Eun-ho?
Well…
Yes.
Eun-ho's just a close friend. He's like a little brother to me.
That's all.
I mean, he's handsome,
younger than you,
and a huge star who would do anything for you.
If you're not interested in him,
I'm curious to know what your ideal type is like.
Wow.
I've never heard Mr. Yoon ask a question like that.
Huh?
Could it be that he has a crush on Ms. Na?
I'm just curious.
No ulterior motives.
My ideal type…
If I say anything that sounds like Mr. Baek,
they'll figure me out.
Well, for starters, I…
-I like free spirits. -"Free"?
You know, someone who's a big P on the MBTI.
Someone who makes impulsive decisions and just takes off on trips.
"Impulsive"?
Someone a bit younger than me
with a fair, baby face.
Chubby cheeks that stretch when you pinch them.
Right. A face like tofu.
Tofu face.
"Tofu"?
And I like someone
with no muscles at all.
I like them skinny. Like a twig.
So that's why Mr. Ji didn't make the cut.
Exactly. Eun-ho has muscles.
You seem quite particular
about your ideal man.
Yeah, I have high standards.
What are you doing?
Should I lose some weight and muscle?
Sorry?
Do I have too much muscle?
Wait, but I need chubbier cheeks.
-How am I supposed to-- -Sir.
-What? -The TS succession is imminent.
You need to focus.
Who says I'm not focused?
Did you give them the slush fund ledger?
Yes. Doseong Daily will handle the rest.
They should've hidden their weaknesses before attacking me.
They've got so many enemies. How dare they challenge me?
Mr. Yoon.
Sir?
What's "a big P" in MBTI?
Sorry?
Ms. Na mentioned it earlier.
She said she likes people with a big P in MBTI.
Sir.
I have to get back to work.
I must attend to a very important matter
to get ready for the succession of TS Group.
A BIG P IN MBTI
BACK VIEW OF I-HYEOK STANDING IN THE MEETING ROOM
What is it?
(NERVOUSLY)
(PULLING HYE-JU TOWARDS HIM)
Just a moment.
What is it? Is there someone suspicious?
-Am I in danger? -No.
(GAZING TENDERLY)
Even if you were, I would never let anyone hurt you.
Why did you ask me to come here?
No reason.
(GAZING INTENSELY)
(FLUSTERED)
I-HYEOK PUSHES HYE-JU AGAINST THE WALL
HYE-JU'S HEART RACES, READY TO BURST
I just
wanted to see you.
Is that not okay?
(SEDUCTIVELY)
I-HYEOK LEANS IN TOWARD HYE-JU'S LIPS
HYE-JU SURRENDERS TO HIM
Ms. Na!
Yes?
A moment of your time, please.
What is it?
Just a moment.
Isn't this exactly what I just wrote in my script?
What are you doing all of a sudden?
I
looked it up.
Looked what up?
A big P in MBTI.
In the Myers–Briggs Type Indicator,
P stands for perceiving.
It refers to people with a strong tendency to perceive.
Oh.
Yes.
P types tend to be free-spirited, flexible, exploratory,
and spontaneous.
Are you giving a presentation?
-Why are you standing like-- -I asked for you on a whim.
Openly hitting on you at work.
It's not easy
for a senior managing director at a major corporation
to be this flexible.
I don't think
this is really a P thing.
Really?
How about this?
What?
Will you go out with me?
I haven't asked you out yet.
Let's date.
Even after our contract ends,
let's stay together.
Didn't expect that, did you? Spontaneous and free-spirited, right?
No, it's not that.
I just…
Since we already kissed,
I thought we were dating.
What?
Oh.
No, you're right. You're absolutely right.
No, it's just…
Earlier, you said your ideal type was a free-spirited, spontaneous P-type.
Right?
Ms. Na Bo-bae?
What is it?
Why are you laughing?
Oh, Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
How are you this cute?
Cute? What do you mean?
Don't you mean "cool"?
No, you're really cute.
Cute? I'm a grown man.
Aw, is Ho-rang angry like a tiger?
Poor baby.
Rawr.
Ms. Na Bo-bae. I take back what I said earlier.
Mr. Baek…
Mr. Baek Ho-rang, wait.
Gosh, Baek Ho-rang is so cute.
Seriously.
"So cute"?
Wow, that's so cringe.
Then again, he was the one who started acting all cute.
I mean, how can a grown man be so cute?
Seriously.
Will you go out with me?
Huh?
No. Stop that.
Darn it.
Ms. Na.
I can feel it. This is going to be a hit.
You've got yourself a contract!
Oh my gosh! Director!
Ms. Na!
For real? My gosh!
I knew you could do it.
Look at you.
Do I smell?
Let's really lock in.
I'll give this project my all.
Man, this is…
This is why experience matters.
Just write it down as is, and it's a drama.
Ms. Na Bo-bae.
You should have breakfast.
Okay?
Come on. Wake up.
Open up.
Okay, that's it.
You're fired as of today.
What?
Why…
You're firing me?
Your drama's at a crucial stage, right?
You think about it day and night.
Well, yeah, it's a crucial time.
But did you really have to fire me?
This is making me uncomfortable.
I only hired you as my secretary to fool Choi Do-yoon.
You've worked for over two months. That should be enough.
Still, this is all so sudden.
The whole point of our arrangement was so you could write your script.
That has to come first.
I'll have Mr. Yoon explain things to the other secretaries.
Don't worry. Just focus on your script.
Thanks for being so considerate.
Ms. Writer Na Bo-bae.
I'm off to work. See you later.
Take your time and finish this.
What was that? Honestly.
Firing her was the right decision.
It's too risky to keep Ms. Na around.
What risk?
Once the contract ends, you'll part ways.
This is a perfectly natural way to gradually cut ties with her.
What are you talking about? Why would I do that?
I'm going to keep seeing her after our contract ends.
Are you really dating her?
Watch the road or we'll crash!
Yes, sir.
That's right.
I'm dating Ms. Na Bo-bae.
Mr. Yoon, have you lost your mind?
I'm sorry.
I thought I saw something ahead.
Be careful.
My heart can't take it.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Does that have caffeine in it?
It's decaf.
Don't lie to me. I felt the caffeine on my tongue!
Don't you know I have trouble sleeping?
Decaf, please!
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
Hi, Mom. What's up?
A ledger?
What? Do…
Doseong Daily?
Do you admit to the charges?
Breaking news. Through Doseong Daily, JBS has obtained
the TS Hotel slush fund ledger mentioned by Senior Managing Director Baek Ho-rang
at TS Resort's emergency press conference.
Assemblyman Choi Tae-sik was found to have fabricated
the allegation that Mr. Baek mistreated people.
Meanwhile, the dispute over the TS Group succession continues.
We'll keep you updated as more…
Baek Ho-rang.
So this was your trump card?
Baek Ho-rang!
Sir.
Move. You son of a bitch!
Mr. Choi.
Call security.
They're coming.
Why'd you only get my dad arrested?
Why leave my mom and me out of it?
Are you trying to humiliate me?
Let go.
Okay.
You can't be that dumb.
We have to get through TS's 30th anniversary party scandal-free.
Just hang tight.
I'll take care of the two of you once it's over.
Take care of us?
This is
all you can do.
Cursing, spitting, making a scene.
That's just your level.
Did you really think you and your family could get your hands on TS?
Yeah.
At least my family isn't dead.
We're alive, so we can at least put up a fight.
Instead of coming to me,
go whine to your family
while they're still alive.
And you should take good care of Na Bo-bae.
Everyone you care about ends up dead, don't they?
Who knows? Na Bo-bae might also--
Don't you dare
drag Ms. Na into this.
Sir, that's enough.
-Clean this mess up. -Yes, sir.
I have to go see my grandmother.
How did you like the show I put on?
The real embezzler has been exposed,
the stock price is recovering,
and thanks to the Ji Eun-ho incident, public opinion of TS Resort has improved.
Patting yourself on the back, huh?
Aren't you happy?
I even took care of Uncle,
who was a thorn in your side.
At the upcoming 30th anniversary party,
earn everyone's respect with those abilities you keep bragging about.
Very well.
See you at the party.
You're here.
I'm home.
Come with me.
Huh? What is it?
What is it?
"We're at the office. Are you crazy?"
-Do I have to? -Come on. Just do it.
"I don't care
if we're at the office or on the street."
"All I see is you, ma'am."
Are you kidding me?
That's not in the script.
No, I'm asking if you're messing with me.
You can't read the lines like that.
You need to put some feeling into it and make it sound real.
You're not helping at all.
Am I an actor?
I'm just a senior managing director.
I just have to read the lines. Do I have to put emotion into it too?
Eun-ho was always great at this. I wish I could call him.
What?
Why'd you have to bring him up?
He's an actor, and I'm--
Yes, Senior Managing Director of TS Resort.
Please continue.
I'm not doing it.
Come on. Why?
Don't be like that.
Just read it once. Hurry.
The other day at work, you were like,
"Will you go out with me?"
I told you to forget about that.
I know you can do a good job. That's why I'm pushing you.
Just try it one more time.
"I don't care
if we're at the office or on the street."
"All I see is you, ma'am!"
Mom.
Mom, it's a misunderstanding.
You know he's a man of integrity.
He's a four-term assemblyman and a presidential front-runner.
Do you think…
I'll go easy on you because you're my daughter?
This isn't the time to be defending your husband.
Why can't you go easy on me?
How can you treat me worse than a dog?
You trust your dead son more than me?
Do you care more about Lucky Charm, that damn dog, than me?
Of course.
What did you say?
If Gyeong-seok were still alive, I would have retired a long time ago.
He was sharp at his job and had the guts to think big.
Obviously, you're no match for Gyeong-seok.
You know, I expected more from you because you're my daughter.
But Gyeong-seok was the one who took after me,
not you.
Do I care more about my dog than you?
He does exactly what I say. He even plays dead when I tell him to.
He's cute and does adorable things.
But you…
You flounder through life, consumed by your insecurities.
It's pathetic.
You're foolish, can't do anything right,
and you married a man just like you.
Do I…
Do I have to be good at everything? Do I have to be perfect?
I'm your daughter!
Please, Mom! Please!
Can you stop treating me as a racehorse and see me as your daughter for once?
Do you even know why I've been insecure my whole life?
It's all because of you! This is how I was raised!
Gyeong-jin.
You resent me, don't you? Maybe even hate me.
You must wonder how it's possible for a mother to be like this.
But…
I feel the same way.
I resent you too.
I hate the sight of you.
Why is the only child I have left so disappointing?
I miss Gyeong-seok so much it hurts.
You're unbelievable.
What was I expecting?
From Chairwoman Gong Man-seol.
You, Choi Tae-sik, and Do-yoon…
Get ready to return everything you've received.
Mr. Baek Ho-rang!
Yes? What is it?
-Look at this. -Huh?
CHOI TAE-SIK ARRESTED
-Your name is cleared, right? -It was all over the news yesterday.
-You didn't know? -I was busy writing my script.
Why didn't you tell me? This is great news!
You knew this would happen.
Yeah, but still…
Sit down. Charge me.
Huh?
You're fully charged.
We still have to do the morning charge. It's in the contract.
What? There's no such thing.
You don't want to hold hands?
No, it's not that I don't want to.
You could just ask me to hold your hand instead of using charging as an excuse.
Then…
let's keep holding hands.
Okay.
-What? -Nothing.
Why are you trying to pull your hand away?
Someone's walking by.
Wow, it's obvious you've never been in a relationship.
Is holding hands really that embarrassing?
Not really, but it's kind of… you know.
So what, you've been in lots of relationships?
A few girls flirted with you. That's about it.
It's not like you have a lot of dating experience either.
Maybe not, but definitely more than you.
Oh, how many?
What?
Oh.
Not that many.
Not many at all.
You're my first, Ms. Na Bo-bae.
Watch what you say.
I will.
I've never done this with anyone before.
Kissing on the street.
And
this too.
-Huh? What are you doing? -It's a first for me.
Put me down!
You know I have a weak heart, so stay still.
Should we
hurry home?
Yes.
Hi, Seol-hee. What's up? You came all the way to see me?
I'll have what he's having.
I've got a reason to drink,
but why is my dear Seol-hee in such a bad mood?
Oh.
Your cousin and grandma
ruined my mood.
What?
I said it'd be best if you gave up now.
But ma'am…
I was quite fond of you.
I thought it was cute that you pretended to be gentle and kind.
I thought you'd make a good daughter-in-law for the TS family.
And seeing how you grew your company,
I thought you could help Ho-rang.
Don't look so upset. It's a compliment.
All your compliments are in the past tense.
Even if it's all in the past,
it's still a huge compliment that I trusted you, isn't it?
But
Ho-rang proved his worth without your help.
Drink up.
So does that mean you don't need me anymore?
I have no reason to pressure him into marriage anymore, so--
If you give me another--
You know it's not up to me to give you another chance, right?
The tea tastes bitter today.
I don't think you should drink it.
Relying on an old hag could only get me so far.
Do-yoon, you have someone tailing Baek Ho-rang, right?
Huh?
Yeah.
I've always had someone tailing him.
Then
you must know a thing or two about Na Bo-bae.
Interesting to hear you bring up Na Bo-bae.
I was taught
to do my best to protect myself.
Why don't we come up with a Plan B?
CARDIOTHORACIC SURGERY JANG KI-WOOK
MEDICAL RECORD BAEK HO-RANG
So he had surgery,
but the cardiac device failed
because of a power outage?
INPATIENT RECORD NA BO-BAE
What's this?
"Cardiac arrest due to lightning strike"?
Look at you giving your name without a shred of shame.
Wait a minute.
L
Hey, it's me.
Have you ever seen Na Bo-bae and Baek Ho-rang holding hands
or touching each other at all?
Damn. You're useless.
I'll see for myself.
Wow, look. It must be on sale.
-Yeah? -Looks good, huh?
Looks pretty unhealthy.
Come on. We don't have any snacks at home.
Looks like buy one, get one free.
-I don't think so. -Let's get this.
Wait.
Yes, Director.
Ms. Na, I read the revised script.
It's good.
-Really? -Yeah.
Wanna hear some more good news?
We have a meeting with the female lead.
The actress playing Hye-ju?
Yeah, Yoo Min-hee accepted the part.
Yoo Min-hee? Isn't she a huge star?
Of course she is. She's a superstar.
She loves the script.
-She wants to meet next week. -Really?
Yes. Got it!
Okay.
No way!
-This is insane! -What is it?
We've got our female lead.
Yoo Min-hee.
-Who is Yoo Min-hee? -You don't know who she is?
Don't you watch TV?
-TV? -Yeah.
-Come on. How do you not know? -So nothing happens when he touches her.
That patient, Na Bo-bae, was a little strange.
Lots of static electricity.
Mr. Baek's heart had run out of battery,
but it recharged when he was near Ms. Na.
So she really is a human charger.
Someone's over the moon, huh?
Yoo Min-hee's going to star in my show.
Am I dreaming?
Can I pinch your cheek?
Why would you pinch me? Shouldn't it be the other way round?
I guess it's not a dream.
I knew you wouldn't agree to be pinched. You're too protective of yourself.
What did you say?
Now we just need the male lead. I hope they cast a really handsome actor.
Why do you care if the actor's handsome?
People watch romance dramas for the handsome male leads.
That's the bare minimum.
You're not casting Mr. Ji Eun-ho as the male lead, are you?
Eun-ho? Isn't that kind of a long shot?
I mean, the rumors have been cleared up,
but our names were linked and all.
I don't want him to get caught up in all that again.
Whatever.
You're the only one I'm interested in, Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
So stop being jealous over nothing.
She drives me crazy.
Clear your mind
of distracting thoughts
and worries.
Hey, Ji-hye.
What did you say?
Yong-gi! Ji-hye.
Hey.
What happened? Was it a hit-and-run?
A car hit him in an alley and drove off.
How badly are you hurt?
Just a broken arm. That's all.
I don't even need surgery. I'll be out in two days.
But how are you going to train with a broken arm?
What about your dojo?
I already closed it down.
You did? When?
He closed it down a while ago.
He stuck around because he didn't want you to be alone
if you gave up writing and moved back to Daejeon.
Bo-bae, you're turning 30 soon.
I'm so happy you renewed your contract and have your own studio now.
I'm glad I can move back to Daejeon on my own now.
Good for you.
Eat the bone broth I made and get well soon.
Don't make Mom and Dad look after you.
If you're gonna nag, go home.
Sit down.
Okay.
Have you eaten?
I'm good.
-Want something to drink? -No, I'm good.
Bo-bae, you're turning 30 soon.
I'm so happy you renewed your contract and have your own studio now.
I'm glad I can move back to Daejeon on my own now.
The show's been scheduled, and the female lead's been cast.
I'm not lying.
You're here…
Where did Na Yong-gi go?
-Are you his guardian? -Yes.
Mr. Na Yong-gi…
He was moved to a VIP room two hours ago.
A VIP room?
Come on. Just a little longer!
Is this even hard?
You need to have a strong core, you know?
It's been a minute!
-Yeah, squeeze your glutes. -Squeeze!
What are you guys doing?
-Bo-bae. -Hey, Bo-bae.
Ms. Na Bo-bae.
-Seriously? -We haven't done much, Bo-bae.
-Just small talk. -Yeah! What's the big deal?
We were just talking.
We didn't really talk.
You're impossible.
Huh?
-You were at the café. -Hello, I'm Baek Ho-rang.
I see.
I heard you upgraded my room.
Who exactly are you?
Well, Ms. Na Bo-bae and I are--
Silence! I do not wish to hear it.
Why are you talking like that?
You're so handsome.
Handsome, my ass.
Didn't you say you met Bo-bae at the hospital?
Is everything okay with you?
Oh, back then…
Well, I was there for a checkup.
How much do you make?
Hey!
Why are you asking him that?
What's your net worth?
Do you work out?
Yes, I do yoga.
Yoga?
I heard yoga is good for cardiovascular health.
Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
Why would you put up with all that?
You're usually good at saying no, like a real douchebag.
When was I ever a…
When was I ever a douchebag?
And you guys.
Why would you make someone with heart issues do planks?
-Heart? -He has heart issues?
I mean,
his heart…
You know, his heart. His feelings.
His heart is under stress.
He's been busy with work.
-He's under a lot of stress. -I'm so stressed.
His heart's under stress.
Exactly. You can relieve stress by working out.
But why would you two help him relieve his stress?
Let me see.
-Bo-bae! -No!
My electricity doesn't affect him.
What?
What? It doesn't affect him?
This punk knows about your powers?
Yeah, he knows.
I can touch his bare skin like this, and nothing happens.
-Yes. -Yeah.
-But… -I'm fine.
-But how… -That's…
Come on. Let me see.
Did you overdo it? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yoga's actually harder than planks.
What's going on?
-The electricity… -I'm fine.
Why are you fine?
How did you know my brother was in the hospital?
Why didn't you tell me?
I just…
It's a family matter.
You were already busy, so I didn't want to bother you.
Wow, I'm so hurt.
What?
It really hurts…
that my heart's aching.
I mean, it's not really that…
Is it because of the planks?
My heart starts to ache when I'm worried or anxious.
I start imagining all kinds of things that could go wrong.
Right now,
it hurts so much that you didn't rely on me.
It makes me wonder if you don't trust me.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I just…
It's because I like you so much.
I didn't want to make you worry or burden you with my problems.
You already have enough to worry about.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Are you crazy?
I think I finally understand why you called me cute.
You're really cute.
Seriously…
So you didn't want me to worry because you like me?
You said you felt hurt because I didn't rely on you.
I think that's adorable too.
Let me be a part of your life from now on.
When someone in your family is sick, let me know.
And if something goes wrong, we'll get through it together.
Let's do it together. You and me.
Together?
Yeah. Together.
Well…
Anyway,
TS's 30th anniversary party
is coming up.
Would you…
like to go with me?
Is this what you were building up to?
Sure. I'll go with you.
We'll go together.
Together?
Together.
-Welcome. -Welcome.
This way, please.
Sorry, I don't really like people touching my bare skin.
We can't do your makeup without--
-Ma'am. -Yes?
-Please take good care of her. -Of course.
Thank you.
Let's go.
You don't seem impressed.
It's Mr. Baek
you want to impress.
Why isn't Mr. Baek coming with us?
He's already there, waiting for you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It seems like it's just about confirmed.
With Assemblyman Choi Tae-sik arrested…
That's right.
Maybe that's why you're positively glowing today, Mr. Baek.
You should be the face of the brand instead of Ji Eun-ho.
-Well, aren't you a smooth talker? -That's right.
Thank you.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Oh.
Can I drink this water?
Yes. We'll be on our way now.
Okay.
PORTABLE CHARGER
MR. YOON
What are you doing here?
Oh, hello.
You said you had a date. Why are you here alone?
She's on her way.
Then let's chat until she gets here.
The marriage isn't happening,
but we still need to show everyone TS and Hanlim are on good terms.
The event will begin shortly.
Please take your seats.
Call an ambulance.
No photos. No photos, please!
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang